<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.mule.ide"
      label="org.mule.ide"
      version="1.2.1"
      provider-name="Mule UMO"
      plugin="org.mule.ide.core">

   <description url="http://mule.codehaus.org">
      Mule IDE
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://mule.codehaus.org/License">
      Copyright (c) 2003-2005 SymphonySoft Limited. All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://mule.codehaus.org/License">
      Copyright (c) 2003-2005 SymphonySoft Limited. All rights reserved. 
http://www.symphonysoft.com

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted 
provided that the following conditions are met: 

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions 
and the following disclaimer. 

2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of 
conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with 
the distribution. 

3. The end-user documentation included with the redistribution, if any, must include the following 
acknowlegement:
&quot;This product includes software developed by SymphonySoft Limited (http://www.symphonysoft.com).&quot;
Alternately, this acknowlegement may appear in the software itself, if and wherever such 
third-party acknowlegements normally appear.

4. All advertising materials mentioning features or use of this software must display the 
following acknowledgement: &quot;This product includes software developed by SymphonySoft Limited
(http://www.symphonysoft.com) and its contributors&quot;. 

5. Neither the name of SymphonySoft Limited, Mule, Universal Message Objects nor the names of its 
contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific 
prior written permission. 

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE REGENTS AND CONTRIBUTORS &quot;AS IS&quot; AND ANY 
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED 
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE 
DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE REGENTS OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY 
DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES 
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; 
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON 
ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT 
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS 
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.launching"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.swt"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore.xmi"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.mule.ide.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.1"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.mule.ide.launching"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.1"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.mule.ide.launching.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.1"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.mule.ide.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.1"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.mule.ide.emf"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.1"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.mule.ide.samples"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.1"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
